Brandee Cheung
Brandeedcheung@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/brandeecheung/ • https://brandeecheung.github.io/PortfolioPage/
520-401-6182

Qualifications Summary

Proactive and creative Software Engineer, Web Developer, Graphic Designer, and Social Media Manager adept at identifying customer needs through extensive analysis and research to consistently deliver top-notch content designed to promote brands and increase profits. Experienced in collaborating with diverse teams on projects, operations, and branding initiatives.

Experience

Owner and Operator | BXDXC LLC. Media December 2019 – Present

- Managed social media platforms (FB/IG/Google) for paid ads and promotions.
- Organized photo and video shoots, edited content using Adobe CC.
- Developed and designed effective websites, including e-commerce.

Director of Graphic Design | Social Media Manager | DYPER, Phoenix, AZ 2018 - 2019

- Orchestrated photo shoots and created social media content.
- Increased sales through promotions and creative collateral.
- Managed large-scale ad budgets on social media platforms.

Graphic Designer | Data Analyst | Uber, Phoenix, AZ 2017 - 2018

- Designed visuals and graphics; collected and analyzed national data.
- Created presentations and optimized Google spreadsheets.

Social Media/Design Consultant | Dreylon Vang Sequence1 Media, Mesa, AZ 2016 - 2017

- Planned, designed, and implemented website and social media content.
- Contributed to shoot settings and edited using Adobe Photoshop and After Effects.

Manager | Events Marketing | Maya Day and Nightclub, Scottsdale, AZ 2014 - 2017

- Worked as a bartender and server, providing exceptional customer service in a high-energy nightclub environment.
- Managed servers and coordinated events, ensuring efficient operations and a seamless guest experience.
- Coordinated staffing and events; trained staff to improve customer service.
- Managed social media platforms and created event-related content.

Social Media Output | Graphic Designer | Downtown Ocotillo Chandler, AZ 2013 – 2014

• Produced and posted graphics for promotions and daily updates.

Graphic Designer & Social Media Intern | Soul Carrier 2013 – 2015

- Modeled for professional photoshoots and created branded content, enhancing Soul Carrier Handbag Company's product visibility and engagement on social media.
- Collaborated with the creative team to develop and post compelling visual content, significantly increasing social media following and interaction.

Education

Bootcamp in Full Stack Development The University of Texas at Austin - Austin, TX April 2024 to Present

Bachelor of Science in Graphic Information Technology & Web Development Graduated Cum Laude, 2017 Arizona State University - Ira A. Fulton School of Engineering, Tempe, AZ

Professional Training

Advanced Social Media Strategy Training – Influential Summit Attendee, 2018

Technical Proficiencies

- Full Stack Development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Python
- Adobe Suite: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Lightroom
- Other Tools: CAD, autoCAD, RHYNO, Sketchup, Microsoft Office, Google Suite

Key Skills Lifecycle Project Management | Graphic Design | Social Media Management | Brand Development | Ads & Promos | Content Production | Web Design & Development | Photography & Editing | Staff Training & Leadership | Customer Service | Data Analysis | Market Trend Research